[folk music playing]
[guns cocking]
[music continues playing]
[laughs]
[Diego] What? Intruders? Get rid of them.
I'm far too busy at the moment,
so don't bother me with pointless reports.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
DATE X WITH X PALM
-…you've earned a painful demise.
-[bones cracking]
And it's piquing my appetite.
[slashing]
[chuckles]
That's it, the flavor I seek.
Yes! I can feel it.
This is it!
[gasps]
By consuming the aura of the Rares,
he makes it his own.
[muffled laugh]
[door bursts open]
Hey! Who are you? Guards!
What do you think you're doing?
[King] He's worthless.
I don't sense anything at all.
Insolent thugs!
Have you any idea who I am?
I am the absolute leader of this era,
a king among kings.
I am Masador Diego!
Someone tell me why this scum
is claiming to be a king.
It seems to me that in the human world,
it's a very common phenomenon.
Humans without intelligence or talent
end up in positions of power
due to heredity or connections.
[King] That defies all logic.
In the hands of an incompetent,
power brings nothing but ruin.
This must be the work of imbeciles.
We must keep humans on a very short leash.
Sire. They can provide you
with quality meat, however,
not to mention the fact
they are a fully self-renewing resource,
as an acceptable food source
for soldiers like us.
[grunts angrily] You'll leave here at once
if you know what's good for you!
[women whimpering]
[Neferpitou] Please,
allow me to take care of this.
He can be used to control the humans.
[King] Do as you like.
[woman] Wait! No!
Please, spare our lives. We beg of you.
[laughs]
These humans are complete idiots.
Now, I want you to think as hard
as those puny brains of yours can manage.
Have you ever spared a pig or a cow
We'll call this place the Meat Orchard,
and we'll use it
as a human processing plant.
[Neferpitou] Sire.
[narrator] After losing
to Knuckle and Shoot,
Gon and Killua return to the inn
where Palm waits.
[Killua] Before I worry about enemies,
I have to protect Gon from Palm.
[creaking]
[both gasping]
[Palm] You promised me.
[grunts] I'm sorry.
[Palm] I have no interest in an apology.
There's no point in having you
stick needles in your eye either.
There is.
You must accomplish
any one task that I set before you.
Go out with me.
This is none of your business.
Just between Gon and me.
Oh, goodness! Mmm!
[giggling]
[Killua shudders]
I'm telling you, man,
you need to stay away from her.
[Palm] And you need to stop interfering!
This is between Gon and me, remember?
[Killua] You just want an excuse
to keep saying that!
[Palm] Oh, shut up!
Gon and I are going on a date,
and that's final.
Besides, there's somewhere
I really want to go.
[gasps]
What are you talking about?
We are going out.
You promised me, didn't you?
Mmm-hmm.
Then why is he tagging along?
And why would we train, anyway?
You must be joking!
We're dating,
and this will be our first date!
Our first date.
[breathing heavily]
But it's not actually a date.
Just wait, and you'll find out tomorrow.
[Palm] Oh.
Well, in that case, all right.
No, it was my fault.
I just wanted to surprise you,
thought it might be fun.
Oh, my goodness! A surprise for me?
-I'm keeping an eye on you. [giggles]
-[Killua shudders]
[Gon] All right. Then let's meet
in front of the bulletin board
at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
[Palm] I'll be there.
Hmm?
Have you ever been on a date before?
Sure, plenty of times.
[Killua groans]
Except, most all of them
were with my Aunt Mito.
Oh. Okay, I get it now.
Wait. So does that mean
that there were others?
Yep. Sometimes ships with all-female crews
would stop by whale island,
and some of them would only go out
with guys who were younger than them.
I'd show them around town,
and they'd teach me a bunch of stuff.
[Killua] "Stuff"? Hold on. That means…
He's so experienced.
[chuckles] They call women like that
"cougars." Isn't that crazy?
Haven't you ever been on a date, Killua?
And I thought we would stay together.
I've already made up my mind.
[cell phone ringing]
Yeah? Hello.
[Knuckle] It's Knuckle.
-We've located and secured Kite.
-[gasps]
Really? So Kite is okay, then?
so I'd like to tell you he's okay,
but I can't.
Don't worry. I'm sure
there's some way we can bring him back.
[Knuckle] All right. It'll take three days
for us to reach your location.
In the meantime,
be on the lookout for any soldier Ants.
All right!
I knew that Kite was still alive!
[Killua] That's great.
[people gasping]
[humming continues]
Oh, wow!
Look over here!
[stops humming]
[laughs]
[Cheetu] I've found new feeding grounds.
[slurps]
[water flowing]
[Gon] Found it!
Okay, but what's it for?
[Killua] If we run into any soldier Ants
here in the mountains,
we'll be in serious trouble.
On the other hand, if we stay in town,
After all, Gon can't use Nen right now.
So I've gotta protect him,
even if it means
sacrificing everything else.
-[brush rustles]
-[gasps]
Let's hurry up.
[sirens wailing]
[tires screeching]
-Ready.
-And fire!
[gunshots]
He disappeared.
[groaning]
[officers screaming]
You'd think they'd be faster.
This is no fun.
And in other news, at around noon today,
an unidentified creature killed
seven people in the suburbs of Pata.
According to the authorities,
the creature moved faster
than 200 kilometers per hour.
Another city's between us,
with the Miera Mountains
on the opposite side.
We should be okay.
The government has submitted
a capture request
with the Hunter Association.
[Gon] I guess tomorrow
we'll both be on our own, huh?
[Killua] Yeah. I'll be training at the gym
pretty much the whole day.
[Killua] Yeah, right.
I can't just leave Gon alone
when he's vulnerable.
-[Palm] Gon, over here.
-Huh?
I didn't even recognize you.
[Killua] Who are you?
Do I look strange to you?
Mmm-mmm. You look really pretty.
Oh, no, please stop it.
You're being far too loud.
[Killua groans]
[Killua] Damn it!
What the hell am I doing here?
There's no telling
when the enemy might show up.
Either way, I'll probably run into it.
Should I warn them?
It's so pretty.
[Killua] No. If I told them now,
it wouldn't help anyway.
Besides, Gon can't use his Nen right now.
If he gets all upset about Kite
and flies off the handle,
then he's done for.
And knowing Palm,
she'll go 100% nuts
if I interrupt her date.
If she breaks the silence
with her screaming,
any Ants that are nearby
will notice us for sure.
[Palm] Thanks, but I'm fine.
[giggles]
[Gon chuckles]
[Killua] I can't let them know.
[imperceptible]
I'll handle this myself.
[gasps]
[Rammot] Ah! I thought I smelled a human.
[gasps] It's him.
It looks like your luck's run out, kid.
Of course, it won't last forever,
you know.
It doesn't matter if you talk or not,
I suppose.
[Killua] He's right.
I've gotta protect Gon,
no matter what it takes.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Friend and Journey."
Going back to Whale Island with Killua.
[Killua] Stargazing with Gon.
[both] We're going on a journey!
[singer singing in Japanese]